[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "In which fictional town does the show take place?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Houston",
      "Hanford",
      "Hamilton",
      "Hawkins"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hawkins"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the name of the four friends favourite fantasy tabletop game?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The 13th Age",
      "Quests Of Yore",
      "Dungeons & Dragons",
      "Shadowrun",
      "Star Wars Roleplaying"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dungeons & Dragons"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Who were the creators of the hit TV show?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The Samsung twins",
      "The Duffer brothers",
      "Bernard Manning",
      "Quentin Tarantino",
      "Steven Martin"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Duffer brothers"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What was Kaliâ€™s number at the Hawkins Lab?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "002",
      "007",
      "012",
      "008"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "008"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the alternate dimension in Stranger Things named?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Mangletown",
      "Demogorgon",
      "The Upside Down",
      "Mind Flayer",
      "Sunnyside Up"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Upside Down"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Who is the first person from Hawkins High School to die at the hands of The Demogorgon?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Barbara Windsor",
      "Barcardi B",
      "Barbara Holland",
      "Bambi Stevens",
      "Barb Banners"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Barbara Holland"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which character from the show is British, and was born and raised in Spain?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Jim Hooper",
      "Eleven",
      "Max Mayfield",
      "Bill Byers",
      "Steve Harrington"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Eleven"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "How many times was the show rejected by several networks before starting filming?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "15-20",
      "20-40",
      "1-5",
      "5-15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15-20"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Who does vampire impresion on Haloween in Hawkins?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Bob Newby",
      "Steve Harrington",
      "Lucas Sinclair",
      "Eddie Munson"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Newby"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which character admits they are scared of horror movies?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Eddie Munson",
      "Max Mayfield",
      "Eleven",
      "Murray Murray Bauman",
      "Karen Wheeler"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Max Mayfield"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What famous horror movie character player 'Victor Kreel' in Season 4 of Stranger things?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Hannibel Lecter",
      "Michael Myers",
      "Leatherface",
      "Freddy Krueger",
      "Chucky"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Freddy Krueger"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which character in the show enjoyed the most screentime from season 1-3?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Dustin Henderson",
      "Steve Harrington",
      "Eleven",
      "Mike Wheeler",
      "Nancy Wheeler",
      "Jim Hooper"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Eleven"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Was the show inspired by a true story?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What US state is the show set in?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Ohio",
      "West Virgina",
      "Illinos",
      "Indiana",
      "Missouri"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Indiana"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "In what year does the first season take place?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "1986",
      "1989",
      "1983",
      "1980",
      "1982"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1982"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is Max's favourite song that saves her from Vecna?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Sunny when Im chilled",
      "Running up the field",
      "Running up that Hill",
      "Walking Jack n Jill"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Running up that Hill"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Who is the military leader searching for Eleven?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Lt. Colonel Jack Sullivan",
      "Sgt. Fred Derst",
      "Lt. Colonel Frank Sinner",
      "Sgt. Jack Sparrow"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Lt. Colonel Jack Sullivan"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Who asks Eleven to dance at the Hawkins Snow Ball in Season 2?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Will",
      "Mike",
      "Dustin",
      "Joyce"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Mike"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What is the room the children play in at Hawkins National Laboratory called?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The Rainbow Room",
      "The White Room",
      "The Play Pen",
      "The Mind Trainer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Rainbow Room"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What new shopping centre is the main location used in Season 3?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The Moonlight Mall",
      "The Super Plaza",
      "Plaza Court Shopping",
      "Starcourt Mall"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Starcourt Mall"
  }
]
